So let's take a look at what products we have.
让我们看一下我们有的产品
So, let's look at what reviews we have for different product names.
看看不同的产品有哪些点评
And here, we're gonna use the canvas again,
我们在这里会继续用到Canvas
to do a little bit of visualization.
来做一些可视化
And so, as with before, I'm going to do graphlab.canvas, and
像之前一样 输入graphlab.canvas.set_target('ipython')
we'll set the target to be my ipath to on notebook so
这样它的目标就是我笔记本上的的ipath
it will show up right here on the ipath on notebook as we're building this.
这样它的路径就设置在了我笔记本的ipath上
Now we can take one of the columns of this s frame of the product.
我们把这些产品的某一列取出来
So for example, let's take the name of the product,
以产品名称这一列为例
and we can just hit .show on it, and that's gonna show
只要输入product['name']后面加上.show()就可以显示了
a histogram of the different names of the different products in this data set.
这样一张不同产品有着不同名称的图就会显示出来
So, for example, right here.
看 就在这
So we see that this particular product, Vulli Sophie something gets the most
我们看到了某一个产品 比如说Vulli Sophie得到了最多的点评
reviews, 785 reviews as compared to like simple wishes something,
总共785个点评 相比较第二项的simple wish(后面还有字没显示出来)
something, 562 reviews and you can see that the number of reviews go down.
simple wish有着562个点评 然后你可以看到点评的数量逐渐递减
Fisher Price products 489, 450.
再往下Fisher price系列产品分别是489 450个点评
This is different baby products here that we're analyzing and
这里是不同的婴幼儿产品
you'll see the histogram of the different reviews of different products,
我将要分析的是 你会看到不同的产品有着不同数量的点评
number of reviews, so let's visit that first Vulli Sophie.
我们仔细看一下Vulli Sophie吧
What is that?
这是什么呢？这是什么呢?
So let me tell you a little bit more about that product.
让我先告诉你一些有关产品的信息吧 很关键
So let's explore the so
让我们先研究一下
called Vulli Sophie and this is an extremely popular product,
这个非常受欢迎叫做Vulli Sophie的产品
so it's actually, I happen to have one right here.
正好这就有一只
This is Vulli Sophie, the giraffe teether.
Vulli Sophie 一个长颈鹿型的磨牙玩具
So it's a little plastic giraffe.
就是一个小的橡胶长颈鹿
It's the most gifted product for babies on Amazon.
是亚马逊上最受欢迎的婴幼儿礼物
And it's a teether, which means like babies like to chew on it.
作为一个磨牙玩具 意味着小孩们会咬他咀嚼它
So lots of reviews for this giraffe for babies to chew on,
评论中反映有很多小孩会咬它
and it's made out of plastic and squeaks.
它是由橡胶组成 还会发出吱吱的声音
[SOUND] So this is what we're gonna talk about a lot today,
这个小玩意今天会被反复提到
this little giraffe [SOUND].
小长颈鹿
Now, let's look at the reviews for this particular giraffe.
现在让我们看看对它的一些点评吧
So, I'm gonna call it giraffe.
我就把这个产品叫做长颈鹿了
Giraffe reviews.
长颈鹿点评
And then we're going to take all of those products that I have,
我将要从所有的产品
all those product reviews, and I am going to select,
和所有的产品点评中选取
this is another filter, I am going to select those rows where
另一个过滤条件 就是
the product name is equal to the name of this particular giraffe.
那些产品名称等于这个长颈鹿的名字
So this is Vulli Sophie
所以说过滤条件是product['name']]=='Vulli Sophie'
the Giraffe Teether.
也就是这个长颈鹿磨牙玩具
This is the product that we've been talking about.
这就是我们要研究的产品了
So if we take a quick look here, if I ask for the length of this new thing,
先看看关于它的点评数量有多少
giraffe reviews, this table, you see there's 785 reviews for this plastic toy.
这张表应该有对这个塑料玩具的785项点评
[NOISE] Little teether.
就是这个磨牙玩具
So, 785 reviews, and let's look at the ratings.
恩 有785项点评 那么评分呢
So, I'm gonna take the giraffe_reviews, the ratings, just for
我会输入giraffe_review['rating'].show()
this particular product, and I'm gonna do a .show in it like we've been doing.
就像我之前做的一样
I wanna look at particular view called the categorical view.
我要看的是这一栏是分类变量
Which is going to give me, categorical view.
所以这一栏 的设置view=‘categorical’
It's gonna give me a, sort of a histogram of the different reviews and
它会给我显示出一张不同点评
how many scores we got.
和产品得了多少分的图
So, if you take a look at this little histogram here,
如果你仔细看一下这张图
you will see something kind of interesting.
你会看到一个很有趣的现象
People love this thing.
人们很喜欢这件产品
535 the reviews were five stars.
535项点评是五星好评
This is a product 535 five star reviews.
一件拥有535项五星好评的产品
Then the next most common is four stars, then three stars.
接下来最常见的就是四星好评 然后是三星
Then it jumps down to one star, and finally two stars.
接下来是一星差评 然后是两星评价
So a good, sizable amount of people really hated this product.
怎么说呢 也有相当一部分人讨厌这件产品
But most people loved it.
但是大部分人喜欢这件产品
It would be fun to do a kind of sentiment analysis try
如果我们对这件产品做情感分析会很有意思
to understand where the really negative reviews or
就可以试着去理解那些正面评价
the really positive reviews what this review is talking about.
和负面评价到底在说些什么
Just like we discussed in the lectures in this module.
就像我们之前课程中说过的一样
To do that, we'll build a sentiment classifier.
接下来我们要建立一个情感分类器
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community